Is it certain that the patient is fine?
确定病人没事吗？
Blood pressure drops again.
血压再次下降。
Wait. I will check.
等待。我会查的。
You should eat this.
你应该吃这个。
You should be well fed today.
今天你应该吃饱了。
I thank you
我谢谢你
pardon
赦免
I apologize. The young woman who was here, do you know where she went?
我道歉。刚才在这里的那个年轻女子， 你知道她去了哪里吗？
I left a while ago.
我不久前离开了。
when
什么时候
About ten minutes ago.
大约十分钟前。
Thanks
谢谢
Excuse me
打扰一下
Are you the one taking care of Woo Jin Hong?
你是照顾宇振洪的人吗？
Yes
是的
The surgery was successful.
手术很成功。
We have to keep him under observation but the surgery was successful.
我们必须对他进行观察， 但手术很成功。
Thanks
谢谢
Thank you very much
非常感谢
hang in there
坚持住
Good
好的
"Catch outside the ring"
“抓到圈外”
"Spirit of the Navy, Myung-Gil Kim."
“海军精神，金明吉。”
Willah
威拉
It scares me every time.
每次都让我害怕。
Let's go
我们走吧
Let's run.
我们跑吧。
‫86.‬
86.
‫88.‬
88.
‫89.‬
89.
- 90! - Ten more times!
- 90！ - 再十次！
One
一
two
二
three
三
‫12.‬
12.
‫13.‬
13.
‫14.‬
14.
good morning sir
早上好先生
to follow
跟随
‫15.‬
15.
‫16.‬
16.
one two three four
一二三四
one two three four five
一二三四五
Wow, it really worked!
哇，真的有效！
Get up, Woo Jin.
吴镇，起来吧。
To upset their balance, we have to follow this method to overthrow them...
想要打破他们的平衡， 我们就必须按照这个方法来推翻他们……
Listen.
听。
We have to talk.
我们得谈谈。
I said no
我说不
If you go back, you will die a useless death.
如果回去的话，你就会死无葬身之地。
I understand why you're worried about us, Mr. Oh.
我明白你为什么担心我们，哦先生。
Why don't you listen to me then?
那你为什么不听我的呢？
Do you rebel?
你叛逆吗？
Mr. Oh.
哦先生。
I'll tell you what I think today.
我今天就告诉你我的想法。
I believe we can take on Myung-Gil Kim and beat him.
我相信我们可以挑战金明吉 并击败他。
Yang Jung and Do Young are dead.
杨正和道英死了。
How will you overcome it?
你将如何克服它？
Following Mr. Choi's instructions.
按照崔先生的指示。
Many have lost their families , and Kim has robbed them of everything they hold dear.
许多人失去了家人 ，金剥夺了他们所珍视的一切。
If we can bring them together and join forces, Mr. Choi said ,
崔先生说，如果我们能够将他们聚集在一起 并共同努力，
We will overcome it no matter what happens.
无论发生什么，我们都会克服它。
Everyone hides because they are unable to confront and win alone.
每个人都躲起来，因为他们无法 独自对抗并获胜。
But if they find people like me and Wu Jin, I'm sure they'll help us.
但如果他们找到像我和吴谨这样的人， 我相信他们会帮助我们。
What if Myung Gil Kim catches you both before this is done?
如果金明吉 在这一切完成之前抓住你们俩怎么办？
We can fight.
我们可以战斗。
Woo Jin has made a full recovery and I've crossed two weight classes.
宇进已经完全康复 ，我也跨越了两个体重级别。
My punches are stronger now.
我的拳头现在更有力了。
We are fully prepared to eliminate his thugs.
我们已经做好了消灭他的暴徒的充分准备。
If we take everyone's advice,
如果我们听取大家的建议
I think we can eliminate Myung Gil Kim.
我认为我们可以消灭 金明吉。
I won't allow it,
我不会允许的，
This is my final decision.
这是我的最终决定。
I will be in Rome by the time you read this letter, Mr. Oh.
哦先生，当你读到这封信时我已经在罗马了 。
I rented a small room with the money my grandfather gave me.
我 用爷爷给我的钱租了一个小房间。
I promised my grandfather that we would go to Rome together
我答应过祖父我们会一起去罗马
After the elimination of Myung Gil Kim,
淘汰金明吉后，
But I ruined everything.
但我毁了一切。
I will not ask you to understand my actions.
我不会要求你理解我的行为。
But if I stay here, I'll be thinking about my grandfather and I don't think I can bear that.
但如果我留在这里， 我就会想起我的祖父，我想我无法忍受。
Every place I go reminds me of my grandfather,
每到一个地方都会让我想起我的祖父
And I can't stop crying.
我无法停止哭泣。
This makes me crazy.
这让我抓狂。
I'll feel better if I stay away.
如果我离开的话我会感觉好一些。
I love you
我爱你
And I'm sorry.
我很抱歉。
This is so painful, man.
这太痛苦了，伙计。
What you're feeling is not pain, Woo-jin.
你感觉到的不是疼痛，宇进。
It is the feeling that accompanies the disappearance of your weaknesses.
这种感觉伴随着你的弱点消失。
What does this mean?
这是什么意思？
It means that you are stronger today than yesterday.
这意味着你今天比昨天更坚强。
Listen.
听。
Follow me.
跟我来。
Yes sir.
是的先生。
This is the last of Mr. Choi's money saved for emergencies.
这是崔先生 为应急而攒下的最后一笔钱。
Take it and move on.
接受它并继续前进。
I apologize for trying to keep you here because I'm worried about you.
我很抱歉因为担心你而试图把你留在这里。
I'll arrange a room and a car for you in Seoul.
我会在首尔为您安排房间和汽车。
May God bless you both.
愿上帝保佑你们俩。
Thank you, Mr. Oh.
谢谢你，哦先生。
We will win no matter what.
无论如何我们都会赢。
"(Stone Village)"
《（石头村）》
Unit 809.
809单元。
"Woo Jin."
“宇进。”
Yes
是的
Welcome
欢迎
We sent Mr. In Mok Oh.
我们派了 In Mok Oh 先生来。
Come in.
进来。
Let's go
我们走吧
Now if you go back and notice any trace of tampering with the tape,
现在如果你回去发现 磁带有任何被篡改的痕迹
I will report you to the police.
我会向警察举报你。
Why
为什么
My panties are in it.
我的内裤在里面。
No, that will never happen.
不，那永远不会发生。
There is a bed here and another one upstairs.
这里有一张床，楼上还有一张床。
Who wants the one on top?
谁想要上面那个？
- It doesn't matter which one. - Yes.
- 哪一个并不重要 - 是的
Then to you who is above.
然后给上面的你。
Good
好的
I'm sorry but may I ask the reason for your decision?
抱歉，我可以问一下您做出这个决定的原因吗？
For no reason
没原因
Concept
概念
Here are the keys to the door and the car my grandfather asked me to rent.
这是门的钥匙和 祖父让我租的汽车。
This is my number too but don't call if possible.
这也是我的电话号码，但如果可能的话不要打电话。
I am busy
我很忙
-Is this acceptable? -Yes.
-这可以接受吗？ -可以。
okay then
好吧
Thanks
谢谢
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Did she point to Mr. Oh, saying he was her grandfather?
她有没有指着吴先生说他是她的祖父？
Yes, she must be his granddaughter.
是的，她一定是他的孙女。
correct. I find that they are similar once I think about it.
正确的。 我仔细想想，发现它们很相似。
They have a small body and wear glasses.
他们身材娇小，戴着眼镜。
But didn't it look like she was forced to lend her apartment?
不过，她这不是被逼 借了房子吗？
- Isn't it? - Right.
- 不是吗？ - 对。
I feel bad
我心情不好
Enough talking about that.
说得够多了。
- Let's shower and make a plan. - Okay.
-我们去洗澡然后制定计划吧 -好的
- Oh God, my stomach hurts so bad. - I'm in pain.
-天哪，我的胃好痛。- 我很痛苦。
What's the reason
什么原因
I think we should catch Jae Myung Yang first to gather information.
我觉得我们应该先抓住杨在明 ，收集情报。
what about you
你呢
"Mr. Moon, President M."
“文先生，M总统。”
I think we need to gather allies first.
我认为我们首先需要聚集盟友。
Moving together will result in solidarity.
共同行动将带来团结。
I like this idea too.
我也喜欢这个主意。
But how will we find it?
但我们怎样才能找到它呢？
Mr. Choi said he would be our best helper.
崔先生说他将是我们最好的帮手。
I thought about that on our way to Seoul, but meeting the heir to the Isle Group wouldn't be easy.
我在去首尔的路上想到了这一点， 但见到岛集团的继承人并不容易。
I'll come up with a plan somehow.
我会想出一个计划。
- “Woo Jin”! - What?
- “宇进”！ - 什么？
You can open the roof in this model.
您可以在此模型中打开屋顶。
-The roof is retractable? -Yes.
- 屋顶可以伸缩吗？ - 是的。
It's cloth.
是布啊
O'Brother
奥兄弟
Lots of loan sharks in Myeongdong.
明洞放高利贷的人很多。
Smile Capital fooled them as well as you.
微笑资本愚弄了他们，也愚弄了你。
I suggest that we bring them together and form a united front.
我建议我们把他们聚集在一起，形成统一战线。
Money lenders in this neighborhood...
附近的放债人...
You know them all with your relationships.
你通过你的人际关系认识他们。
If you lead, those people will follow suit.
如果你领导，那些人就会效仿。
And then what?
然后什么？
You can get your money back
你可以拿回你的钱
She is keen to ensure that Smile Capital does not pull this type of trick again.
她渴望确保微笑资本不再玩 这种把戏。
We will wipe them out of existence. What is your opinion
我们将把它们消灭掉。你有什么意见
I lost a few hundred million.
我损失了好几个亿。
I can't do this.
我不能这样做。
If your plan fails, I may die.
如果你的计划失败，我可能会死。
What about the money you lost?
你损失的钱怎么办？
Screw the money.
拧钱。
I can make up for it, okay?
我可以弥补，好吗？
I will not interfere.
我不会干涉。
I care more about my life than money.
比起金钱，我更关心自己的生活。
- Please, just this once... - Stop.
- 拜托，就这一次... - 停下来。
What is this
这是什么
What happened
发生了什么
my lord
我的主
Entry is not allowed here.
这里不允许进入。
Well, they're little marines.
好吧，他们是小海军陆战队员。
What happened sir?
先生发生什么事了？
What
什么
In reality
事实上
a few days ago,
几天之前，
A group of gangsters came and took everything.
一群歹徒来了，抢走了一切。
Why
为什么
I have ten million bonds that will expire in a month.
我有一千万债券 ，一个月后到期。
If you return this money to me, I will give you five percent of it.
如果你把这笔钱还给我， 我就给你百分之五。
It's too much money to pass up.
钱太多了，不能放弃。
Shall we make a deal then?
那我们做个交易吧？
Surely a classy lady like you doesn't know how to make a deal.
像你这样的优雅女士肯定 不知道如何做生意。
Such issues
此类问题
Be based on mutual trust.
建立在相互信任的基础上。
This is what follows.
这是下面的内容。
I will find someone else.
我会去找别人。
Wait, wait a minute.
等一下，等一下。
Every rule generally has an exception.
每个规则通常都有一个例外。
"(Gwang Mu Moon)"
“（光武文）”
I found out the truth later.
后来我才知道真相。
In the middle of that decade and in a fine line
在那十年的中期，在一线之隔
It was written that if I failed to return the bonds within a month,
上面写着，如果我不能 在一个月内归还债券，
I have to pay them half the amount.
我必须付给他们一半的钱。
That's what was written.
就是这么写的。
That contract looks like a Smile Capital contract.
该合同看起来像微笑资本合同。
What are you
你是做什么的
A company run by Myung Gil Kim.
金明吉经营的公司。
Who worked for Mr. Choi?
谁为崔先生工作？
Yes
是的
Where is that bastard now?
那个混蛋现在在哪里？
Did you hear about what happened to Mr. Choi, sir?
先生，您听说崔先生的事了吗？
Did you hear what?
你听到什么了吗？
Mr. Choi...
崔先生...
Myung Gil Kim killed him.
金明吉杀了他。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Myung-Gil Kim killed Mr. Choi, Mr. Hwang, and Mr. Lee. Kill them all.
金明吉杀害了崔先生、 黄先生和李先生。杀光他们。
We were hiding out in the countryside with Mr. Oh until recently.
直到最近我们才和吴先生一起躲在乡下。
Damn, your talk is not funny at all.
妈的，你说话一点也不好笑。
This is not funny, is it clear?
这不好笑，明白了吗？
Why would Mr. Choi die?
崔先生为何会死？
Why
为什么
For any reason he may die
无论出于什么原因他都可能会死
Mr. Choi?
崔先生？
Answer me, you scoundrels!
回答我吧，你们这些无赖！
Damn
该死
What do you mean by saying he died, you idiots?
你们这些白痴说他死了是什么意思？
I'm tired
我累了
I am very tired
我很累
Let's go in and have a little rest.
我们进去休息一下吧。
Yes sir.
是的先生。
What is this
这是什么
been a long time
已经很长时间了
- These two motherfuckers. - Damn.
-这两个混蛋 -该死
I'll tell you everything, so don't hit me, okay?
我会告诉你一切，所以别打我，好吗？
The news spread among the homeless,
消息在无家可归者中传开，
We collect ID cards in facilities for people with special needs.
我们在为有特殊需要的人士提供的设施中收集身份证。
We didn't ask about you.
我们没有询问你的情况。
What's going on at Smile Capital?
微笑资本现在怎么样了？
You should both be more specific in your questions.
你们的问题都应该更加具体。
Is the club open?
俱乐部开门吗？
wait a moment
稍等
Look down.
向下看。
What is the matter
什么事
Gun Woo, try to play the violent person.
建宇，尝试扮演暴力的人。
How to do it
怎么做
First stop treating him with respect.
首先停止尊重他。
But this man is clearly over 40. It wouldn't be comfortable for me to talk down to him.
但这个男人显然已经四十多岁了， 居高临下地跟他说话对我来说不太舒服。
Good. If he looks at you with disdain, slap him hard.
好的。如果他用蔑视的眼神看着你，就狠狠地打他一巴掌。
Good
好的
First, you may not believe this, but I'm 31 years old.
首先，你可能不相信， 但我已经31岁了。
Secondly, I do not disdain you both , so there is no need for violence.
其次，我并不鄙视你们 ，所以没有必要使用暴力。
My physical condition is currently deteriorating.
目前我的身体状况正在恶化。
A while ago, a scoundrel cut off the Achilles in my heel.
不久前，一个恶棍砍掉了我脚后跟的跟腱。
So I spent four months in a rehabilitation center.
所以我在康复中心度过了四个月。
That bastard is our brother, so watch your words.
那个混蛋是我们的兄弟，所以注意你的言辞。
I am completely to blame for what happened to me then. I really deserved what was done to me.
当时发生在我身上的事情完全是我咎由自取。 我真的罪有应得。
So, the club...
那么，俱乐部...
Okay
好的
I had eavesdropped on the director's call...
我偷听了导演的电话……
the boss? What is his name
老板？他叫什么名字
"Jun Min Kim."
“金俊民。”
Is he alive?
他还活着吗？
A scoundrel had his neck cut and he almost died...
一个恶棍的脖子被割断了，差点就死了……
the curse
诅咒
That's right, you're all on the same team.
没错，你们都在同一个团队。
Well, I understand everything completely now.
嗯，我现在完全明白了一切。
I will be careful with my words from now on, so there is no need to hit me, sir.
我以后会注意自己的言辞的， 所以先生不用打我。
I really hate Jun Min Kim. That motherfucker is a bastard.
我真的很讨厌金俊民。 那个混蛋就是个混蛋。
And Smile Capital is a bunch of scoundrels too.
微笑资本也是一群无赖。
I only work for her for the money.
我为她工作只是为了钱。
I wanted to disclose what was happening. I will tell you everything.
我想透露发生了什么。我会告诉你一切。
We understand that, so please get to the point.
我们明白这一点，所以请进入正题。
I heard a call. They are still in dispute with the Aile Group over the contract,
我听到了电话。 他们还与爱乐集团就合同问题存在争议，
And I heard that Myung Gil Kim is upset.
我听说金明吉很沮丧。
and what
以及什么
Jang Do Im is not on good terms with Joon Min Kim.
张道任和金俊民的关系并不好。
He's really a scoundrel, isn't he?
他真是个无赖，不是吗？
He used to lead the police , but one day he disappeared.
他曾经领导过警察 ，但有一天他失踪了。
But Myung Gil Kim was having fun at a hostess bar recently,
不过金明吉 最近在女主人酒吧玩得很开心，
He fought with a clumsy person and broke his wrist.
他与一个笨手笨脚的人打斗，摔断了手腕。
So the police were called and it was a crisis.
于是警察就被叫来了，危机爆发了。
But it went on as if nothing had happened.
但一切都像什么都没发生过一样继续着。
This is not supposed to be the case when the police are called to appear.
当警察被传唤出庭时，情况不应该是这样。
According to Jeon Min Kim, Myung Gil Kim has found a replacement for Jang Do Im.
据 Jeon Min Kim 透露，Myung Gil Kim 已经找到了张道任的替代者。
But he hasn't told anyone yet.
但他还没有告诉任何人。
Why
为什么
He doesn't trust his men.
他不信任他的手下。
and what else
还有什么
He's planning to take over a golf course in Gyeonggi-do.
他计划接管 京畿道的一个高尔夫球场。
That's why we overwork ourselves like this.
这就是为什么我们 这样过度劳累自己。
We are underpaid but they overwork us.
我们的工资很低， 但他们却让我们过度劳累。
- Isn't it? - Yes.
- 不是吗？ - 是的。
This concludes my summary of current issues.
我对当前问题的总结到此结束。
wait a moment
稍等
You know you'll get killed if we send this to Joon Min Kim, right?
你知道如果我们把这个发给Joon Min Kim你会被杀，对吧？
Keep your mouth shut.
闭上你的嘴。
Don't worry sir.
别担心，先生。
If you need anything, do not hesitate to contact me.
如果您需要任何东西， 请随时与我联系。
I too want to see Smile Capital crash and burn.
我也想看到微笑资本 崩溃并烧毁。
So can you get us the phone number of the Isle heir?
那么你能给我们 艾尔继承人的电话号码吗？
This is beyond my capabilities.
这超出了我的能力范围。
These people maintain their privacy.
这些人维护自己的隐私。
"Son of the eldest chairman of the Ile Group."
“伊乐集团大董事长的儿子。”
"Isle's heir and his trust to create a world-class hotel."
“艾尔的继承人以及他对创建世界一流酒店的信任。”
Understood. His name is Min Beom Hong. His last name is the same as my last name.
明白了。他的名字叫 Min Beom Hong。 他的姓氏和我的姓氏相同。
"Woo Jin."
“宇进。”
"Sol" has the most delicious black vermicelli.
“索尔”有最好吃的黑粉丝。
Okay
好的
Why did you use my computer without my permission?
为什么未经我的允许就使用我的电脑？
I'm signed in to all the messaging apps on it.
我已登录其上的所有消息应用程序。
I'm sorry. We didn't open any of the apps.
对不起。我们没有打开任何应用程序。
Go to an internet café nearby.
去附近的网吧。
Good. I'm sorry
好的。对不起
Hurry up and turn it off.
赶紧把它关掉。
Concept
概念
Let's use it just this once.
我们就用这一次吧。
They accomplished it quickly.
他们很快就完成了。
Good
好的
We are sorry.
我们很抱歉。
How tiring.
多累啊。
how did you know
你怎么知道
She must have received a login notification when we turned on the computer.
当我们打开计算机时，她一定收到了登录通知。
- Shit. - What's going on?
- 糟糕 - 发生什么事了？
Min Beom Hong has 500,000 followers.
Min Beom Hong 拥有 500,000 名关注者。
Let's see now.
现在让我们看看。
Hey, stop.
嘿，停下来。
Didn't I ask you...
我不是问你了吗...
Have the contract ready by today so I can send the money?
今天之前合同准备好了吗？这样我就可以 汇款了？
I would do that,
我会这样做，
But my father...
但我的父亲...
You bastard. how dare you
你这个混蛋。你怎么敢
"By day."
“白天。”
Don't kill me please.
请不要杀我。
Amend the contract as requested and bring it to me by Friday.
按要求修改合同并在周五之前交给我 。
- Okay. - If you don't, I'll post the video.
- 好吧 - 如果你不这样做，我就发布视频。
I will work to show that you committed suicide as a result of the video's spread, okay?
我会努力证明 你是因为视频的传播而自杀的，好吗？
Your order, sir.
您的命令，先生。
Want to get rid of Myung Gil Kim? We can help you.
想除掉金明吉吗？ 我们可以帮助你。
Damn, who are these bastards?
可恶，这些混蛋是谁？
"We know where the hard drive that contains the video is located."
“我们知道包含视频的硬盘位于哪里。”
Let's meet them.
让我们来认识一下他们吧。
If we're going to meet them, let's hurry.
如果我们要去见他们，我们就快点吧。
I must deliver the contract by Friday.
我必须在星期五之前交付合同。
Then ask them if they can meet us now.
然后询问他们现在是否可以见我们。
What to do if they agree?
如果他们同意怎么办？
Meet them at the bar you're going to.
在您要去的酒吧与他们见面。
Their true colors will be revealed once they get drunk.
一旦喝醉，他们的真面目就会显露出来。
the curse
诅咒
Don't worry. I will assign two of my men to attend.
不用担心。我将指派两名手下参加。
“Inseong.”
“仁成。”
- Yes. - It tastes delicious?
- 是的 - 味道很好吃吗？
Yes sir
是的先生
I asked you not to drink alcohol. the curse
我叫你不要喝酒。诅咒
Your order, sir.
您的命令，先生。
"Woo Jin."
“宇进。”
Hello sir
你好先生
I'm close "min day".
我已经接近“分钟日”了。
Good. I'm Gun Woo Kim.
好的。我是金健宇。
And I'm Wu Jinhong.
我是吴锦红。
I am the one who wrote to you.
我就是给你写信的人。
Angels.
天使们。
Okay sir.
好的，先生。
Why don't we discuss it over a drink?
我们为什么不边喝酒边讨论呢？
In reality
事实上
I really apologize for this
对此我真的很抱歉
But Myung Gil Kim's thugs stabbed me
但金明吉的暴徒刺伤了我
It tore up my liver, so I can't drink alcohol.
它撕裂了我的肝脏，所以我不能喝酒。
If you don't want to drink alcohol, say so. decent
如果您不想喝酒， 请直说。体面的
It is the truth, sir.
这是事实，先生。
Here and here.
这里和这里。
And here.
和这里。
We get it.
我们懂了。
It's annoying to see. Take your shirt down.
看到就很烦人。把你的衬衫脱下来。
Well, don't drink with us then.
好吧，那就别和我们一起喝酒了。
Were you stabbed too?
你也被刺伤了吗？
no. I don't just drink.
不。我不只是喝酒。
We will go deeper into our conversation. Let's drink wine.
我们将更深入地进行对话。我们喝点酒吧。
Didn't you meet us here to talk frankly?
你来这里不是为了坦诚地谈谈吗？
If you refuse to fulfill such a trivial request, how can we trust you?
如果你拒绝满足这样一个微不足道的要求， 我们怎么能相信你呢？
If I may be permitted to speak frankly,
如果允许我坦白地说，
Didn't you ask to meet us because you needed us?
你不是因为需要我们才要求见我们的吗？
In this case, I'll take a glass.
在这种情况下，我会拿一杯。
No, I'll drink.
不，我要喝。
Good
好的
And now, Director Hong.
现在，洪主任。
Now, let's drink.
现在，我们喝酒吧。
lump sum
总金额
Good
好的
Wow, you are naturally talented.
哇，你天生就有才华。
Since we're busy, why not drink from bottles?
既然我们很忙，为什么不喝瓶子里的水呢？
This is how whiskey is drunk.
威士忌就是这样喝的。
OK here you go
好的， 开始吧
- Please.
-求你了
Wow.
哇。
- Your messengers. - Okay.
-你的信使 -好的
Let's talk now.
现在我们来谈谈吧。
the curse
诅咒
this is funy
这很有趣
Nice to meet you, Gang Young.
很高兴认识你，姜英。
I was getting nervous because of that bastard Myung Gil Kim.
我因为金明吉那个混蛋而感到紧张。
- Call me my brother, man. - My brother.
- 叫我兄弟吧 老兄 - 我兄弟
Okay. I'm your brother. Okay, pour. - Okay, sir.
好的。我是你的兄弟。好的，倒酒 。-好的，先生。
Because of that bastard,
因为那个混蛋，
I got alopecia,
我得了脱发症
And hemorrhoids, damn it.
还有痔疮，该死。
It hit me when I met him earlier today.
今天早些时候我见到他时，我受到了打击。
The bastard.
这个混蛋。
The police commissioner adores me!
警察局长很喜欢我！
When alone, he says, "Commissioner Min..."
独自一人时，他说： “敏委员……”
And I say, "Brother! Don't do that."
我说：“兄弟！别那样做。”
“Calling me Commissioner Maine might be misunderstood by people.”
“叫我缅因专员 可能会被人们误解。”
Take care of this young man, Gang Young, as we have become close.
照顾好这个年轻人，Gang Young， 因为我们已经变得很亲密了。
Take good care of him. He seems like a good young man.
好好照顾他。他看上去是个不错的年轻人。
You and Woo Jin, you two, do whatever you want.
你和宇镇，你们两个， 想做什么就做什么吧。
Screw whatever, I've got your back all the way.
不管怎样， 我会一直支持你。
Shall I pour you wine?
要我给你倒酒吗？
- I can't anymore. - Okay, sir.
-我不能再这样了 -好的 先生
I can't do this because of hemorrhoids.
由于痔疮，我不能这样做。
Damn, that's because I worked overtime yesterday.
妈的，那是因为我昨天加班了。
I can usually drink for at least another two hours.
我通常至少还能再喝 两个小时。
Damn
该死
"Gang Young."
“刚杨。”
What is this
这是什么
Did you sleep well, Minbeom?
珉范，睡得好吗？
Did you sleep well
你睡的好吗
what's going on
这是怎么回事
We brought you home last night to continue drinking.
昨晚我们带你回家 继续喝酒。
Good
好的
I prepared vermicelli, so I meant to wake you up.
我准备了粉丝，所以想叫醒你。
-We should eat. -Okay.
-我们该吃饭了 - 好吧
Please take a seat
请入座
-Gunwoo, take this. -Okay.
-Gunwoo，拿着这个。- 好的。
- I'll wake up Gang Young. - Okay.
-我会叫醒姜英 -好的
Damn, how much wine did you drink?
妈的，你喝了多少酒？
"Gun-ho"? "Gunwoo"?
“枪浩”？“刚宇”？
My name is Gun Woo.
我叫吴建宇。
Good
好的
Could you remind me of the plan?
你能提醒我一下计划吗？
Gang Young will bring a computer expert from the police agency.
Gang Young将带来一名 来自警察局的计算机专家。
This person will hack Kim's phone and then burn the hard drive in the safe.
此人会侵入 Kim 的手机 ，然后烧毁保险箱中的硬盘。
Vermicelli preparation is complete. You must eat and wake up.
粉丝准备工作完成。你必须吃饭并醒来。
stand up
起来
We'll do it on Friday when Myung-gil comes to the IL group to sign the contract.
我们将在周五 Myung-gil来 IL 集团签署合同时进行。
Who made this decision?
谁做出了这个决定？
You
你
correct. Of course I am. Oh, let's eat.
正确的。我当然是。哦，我们吃饭吧。
How much wine did you drink?
你喝了多少酒？
I notice
我注意到
Good esophagus.
食道良好。
eat the food
吃食物
Thank you for the food
谢谢你的食物
It's been a long time to eat food like this.
已经很久没有吃过这样的食物了。
You both excelled.
你们都表现出色。
The place is huge.
这个地方很大。
The ceiling is very high.
天花板很高。
Wow, how many floors?
哇，多少层？
Thanks
谢谢
- Hello everyone. - You've arrived.
- 大家好 - 你来了
Hello
你好
- Hello. - Allow me to introduce my colleagues.
- 你好。 - 请允许我介绍一下我的同事。
Do it.
做吧。
I'm Sergeant Han Guo-yeon. Nice to meet you.
我是韩国妍中士。很高兴见到你。
Welcome
欢迎
I'm Team Leader Tae Young Kang, from the Cybercrime Department.
我是网络犯罪部门的团队负责人 Tae Young Kang 。
Let's keep my presence here secret. Nice to meet you.
让我们对我在这里的存在保密吧。很高兴见到你。
- Okay. - Nice to meet you.
- 好的认识你很高兴。
Let's also keep my presence secret. We all attended in secret.
我们也保密我的存在。 我们都是秘密参加的。
Good
好的
Taeyong is the country's leading authority for combating cybercrime.
Taeyong 是该 国打击网络犯罪的主要权威。
I'll show you how to hack Kim's phone.
我将向您展示如何侵入 Kim 的手机。
And activate the safe.
并启动保险箱。
Good. There are two ways.
好的。有两种方法。
The first is Wi-Fi.
第一个是Wi-Fi。
I'll put a small jammer in the conference room to cut off the signal
我会在会议室放一个小干扰器 来切断信号
To temporarily block your Internet connection.
暂时阻止您的互联网连接。
This will naturally lead Kim to connect to Wi-Fi.
这自然会导致 Kim 连接到 Wi-Fi。
I will be able to hack the phone once it connects to the communicator.
一旦手机连接到通讯器，我就可以破解手机。
Once I hacked his phone, it would be done.
一旦我黑了他的手机，事情就完成了。
I also conducted preliminary research into vault applications that the suspect might be using.
我还对 嫌疑人可能使用的金库应用程序进行了初步研究。
As for the second method,
至于第二种方法，
We will make sure the suspect opens a more direct crossing to us.
我们将确保嫌疑人 向我们开放更直接的过境点。
Do you know how to scan QR codes when entering buildings due to the pandemic?
疫情期间，你知道进楼如何扫二维码吗？
I will place a direct response code at the entrance and have him scan it.
我会在入口处放置一个直接响应代码并让他扫描。
Once he scans his phone,
当他扫描手机后，
This will give me access to hack his phone.
这将使我能够侵入他的手机。
We will use both methods together.
我们将同时使用这两种方法。
Wait.
等待。
What should I do
我应该怎么办
You must ensure that the suspect stays connected to Wi-Fi;
您必须确保嫌疑人保持 Wi-Fi 连接；
For as long as possible.
尽可能长时间。
I'm going to access his cloud storage to get all the data,
我将访问他的云存储 以获取所有数据，
But it may take time depending on its size.
但这可能需要时间，具体取决于其大小。
If we're lucky,
如果我们幸运的话
We will be able to find evidence of all his crimes
我们将能够找到他所有罪行的证据
He and his partners to put an end to them.
他和他的伙伴们要结束他们。
But what to do...
但该怎么办...
If that bastard finds out what's going on?
万一被那个混蛋知道是怎么回事呢？
Do you have a plan?
你有计划吗？
We are moving forward with both options simultaneously to prevent this from happening.
我们正在同时推进这两种选择， 以防止这种情况发生。
No, this is not what is required. That's not...
不，这不是所需要的。那不是...
The matter will only be fixed by getting rid of the hard drive tomorrow, no matter what the cost.
无论付出什么代价，这个问题只能通过明天扔掉硬盘来解决。
I would take his phone from him if it were up to me.
如果由我决定的话，我会拿走他的手机。
It's simple. It shouldn't be this hard. You're making it too complicated.
这很简单。本来不应该这么难， 你把事情搞得太复杂了。
I'll take his phone.
我会拿走他的电话。
“Han Gu.”
“韩谷。”
May I ask what's on the hard drive?
请问硬盘里有什么？
Damn, unbelievable!
该死的，难以置信！
Okay, listen...
好吧，听着……
They remained silent.
他们保持沉默。
Okay sir.
好的，先生。
“Min Beom,” he accompanied me for a moment.
“Min Beom，”他陪了我一会儿。
"Who day?"
“哪一天？”
You must be very nervous.
你一定很紧张。
This is a very difficult process.
这是一个非常困难的过程。
There are limits because it is informal.
因为它是非正式的，所以有限制。
"Gang Young."
“刚杨。”
If I don't get rid of this engine, I'm going to have to deal with Kim forever.
如果我不摆脱这个引擎， 我将不得不永远与金打交道。
I'll be in big trouble.
我会有大麻烦了。
So I will do my best.
所以我会尽力而为。
Please trust me.
请相信我。
Good
好的
It's not available.
它不可用。
You're sure of this, right?
你确定这一点，对吧？
certainly
当然
Please take your temperature.
请测量体温。
Scan the response code with your camera.
使用相机扫描响应代码。
Shouldn't it be the opposite?
难道不应该是相反的吗？
This is how our system works.
这就是我们的系统的工作原理。
It's an unusual procedure but that's okay.
这是一个不寻常的过程，但没关系。
It works.
有用。
- Okay. - Great!
- 好的， 太好了！
What? What is the matter
什么？什么事
There's nothing in his file.
他的档案里什么也没有。
Give me a moment.
给我一点时间。
The vault application you mentioned is not here.
您提到的保管库应用程序不在这里。
Did you hear this?
你听到了吗？
Yes
是的
Jang Do Im was in no position to lie.
张道任没有资格撒谎。
Is that bastard planning something?
这混蛋是不是在策划什么事情？
Oh my God
我的天啊
Director Hong.
洪主任.
How are you
你好吗
the curse
诅咒
What is the matter
什么事
There's no app for a safe on his phone.
他的手机上没有保险箱应用程序。
This bastard has two phones.
这个混蛋有两部手机。
what do you mean
你是什​​么意思
He scanned the code with a black phone, but this phone is silver.
他用黑色手机扫码，但这部手机是银色的。
What to do now
现在做什么
We have to pay it to connect to wifi.
我们必须付费才能连接 wifi。
Mr. Min is coming here.
敏先生要来了。
- Sir. - Never mind.
-先生 -没关系
-Do you want anything? -I don't want anything.
-你想要什么吗？ -我什么都不想要。
How did it go?
进展如何？
Myung-Gil Kim has two phones.
金明吉 (Myung-Gil Kim) 有两部手机。
We hacked one but there was no app for a vault.
我们破解了一个，但没有用于保险库的应用程序。
The phone with the app is in that bag.
装有该应用程序的手机就在那个包里。
and what
以及什么
We think of a solution.
我们想一个解决办法。
There's no time, Gang Young. It won't take long.
没时间了，姜英。 不会花很长时间的。
Why don't we talk privately?
我们为什么不私下谈谈呢？
Damn
该死
Tae Young, Han Gu.
泰英，韩谷。
Could you give us a moment?
您能给我们一点时间吗？
naturally
自然
What did Jang Do Im use to film the video?
张道林用什么 来拍摄视频？
Cell phone
手机
Wouldn't M have sent the video to Myung Gul Kim's phone then?
那么M不会把视频发送 到Myung Gul Kim的手机上吗？
To confirm his portrayal?
确认他的形象？
Okay
好的
Before you sign the contract, ask him to delete the clip first.
在你签合同之前， 请他先删除该片段。
He would then have no choice but to take out his phone.
这时他别无选择，只能掏出手机。
What if he did not send it?
如果他不发送怎么办？
What if Kim lies about this?
如果金对此撒谎怎么办？
Ask him to show you the conversation he had with Jang Do Im.
请他向您展示 他与张道任的对话。
Tell him that Jang Do Im told you that he intended to send him to his leader.
告诉他张道任告诉你 他打算把他送到他的领导人那里。
truly
确实
Criminals like Myung Gil Kim don't trust anyone.
像金明吉这样的罪犯 不信任任何人。
To make sure that Jang Do Im got the job done properly,
为了确保张道任 妥善完成工作，
It is certain that he was asked to send the video after completing the task.
可以肯定的是，他被要求 在完成任务后发送视频。
I don't think I can do that.
我不认为我能做到这一点。
Believe me
相信我
No, this is not the problem.
不，这不是问题。
I don't think I can stand up to Myung Gil Kim.
我认为我无法 对抗金明吉。
I am afraid
恐怕
Damn, my hands are shaking just looking at him!
妈的，光是看着他我的手就在颤抖！
"Who day?"
“哪一天？”
I'm sure you can do this.
我确信你能做到这一点。
I'll break down the door and break in if I feel there's a problem.
如果我觉得有问题，我会破门而入。
If things get out of control,
如果事情失去控制
I will use all our family's resources to protect you.
我会动用全家的资源来保护你。
So gather your courage this time.
所以这次要鼓起勇气。
We will go there with him, Min Beom.
我们会和他一起去那里，Min Beom。
You can do this.
你可以这样做。
You're late for us.
你比我们迟到了。
Where were you
当时你在哪里
Can the two lawyers come out?
两位律师能出来吗？
I want to have privacy with Mr. Kim.
我想和金先生有隐私。
certainly
当然
Do you want to get arrested?
你想被捕吗？
Where did you get this boldness?
你从哪里得到这样的勇气？
Before we sign the contract,
在我们签订合同之前，
Delete the video.
删除视频。
He's at home.
他在家。
I promise to delete it at home as soon as we sign the contract.
我保证一签合同就在家删除。
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑吧？
I know your man sent it to your phone.
我知道你的男人已将其发送到你的手机上。
Delete it while I see you doing it.
当我看到你这样做时删除它。
Wow.
哇。
- Here I delete it. - No.
- 在这里我把它删除了 - 不
Let me delete it myself.
让我自己删除吧。
I do not trust you
我不相信你
And if I refuse?
如果我拒绝呢？
I won't sign the contract then.
那我就不签合同了。
I see you've completely lost your mind.
我看你已经彻底失去理智了。
Listen
听
You think my family won't move if you touch me?
你以为你碰我，我的家人就不会动吗？
I was acting alone because I was embarrassed.
我独自行动，因为我感到尴尬。
I secretly wanted to solve this crisis.
我暗自想要解决这个危机。
correct
正确的
My aunt is the director of the IRS.
我姨妈是国税局局长。
With one call from me, your company will be audited the next day.
只要我一个电话， 第二天你们的公司就会被审核。
What do you think
你怎么认为
Do you want to pay tens of billions in taxes? Do you want this to be implemented?
你要交几百亿的税吗？ 你想让这个实行吗？
I became eloquent.
我变得能言善辩。
When I see you threatening me.
当我看到你威胁我的时候。
I learned from you
我向你学习
I like this
我喜欢这个
And I don't like this.
我不喜欢这个。
"Wi-Fi is off"
“无线网络已关闭”
"Wi-Fi is on"
“Wi-Fi 已开启”
We received a signal.
我们收到了信号。
Give me a moment.
给我一点时间。
There is an application for a safe.
有一个保险箱的申请。
- Great! - Silence.
- 太棒了！ - 沉默。
I will open the safe now.
我现在就打开保险箱。
Is that all your requests, Director Hong?
洪主任，这就是你的要求吗？
Let's sign the contract.
我们来签合同吧。
Good. Do I start burning?
好的。我开始燃烧吗？
Good
好的
"Complete cremation is being carried out."
“正在进行彻底火化。”
It's done.
完成。
- It really worked, right? - Yes, certainly.
- 确实有效，对吧？ - 是的，当然。
- Thanks. - I will extract the data first.
-谢谢。- 我会先提取数据。
Extract it all.
全部提取出来。
Thank you both.
谢谢你们俩。
No need for thanks
不需要感谢
I will collect all the evidence
我会收集所有证据
I will lock up that bastard, so don't worry.
我会把那个混蛋关起来的，你放心。
Okay sir.
好的，先生。
Well done you two. He'll call you both Gang Young.
你们两个干得好。他会称呼你们俩为Gang Young。
Fine, thank you
好的，谢谢
Thanks
谢谢
This has been bothering me for a while, but...
这件事困扰了我一段时间，但是……
The wound you have, the scar.
你的伤口，疤痕。
I would like to help you process it.
我想帮你处理一下。
Well, I'm grateful for that, but I'm fine.
嗯，我对此很感激，但我很好。
are you sure
你确定吗
Yes
是的
Thanks to this scar, I was able to meet a lot of wonderful people.
多亏了这道伤疤，我才能够认识很多 很棒的人。
You gave me the strength to keep going instead of giving up.
你给了我继续前进而不是放弃的力量。
Therefore,
所以，
I don't mind this scar.
我不介意这个伤疤。
I understand this.
我明白这一点。
See you soon.
再见。
Well
好吧 _
Take care of them.
照顾他们。
- Yes. - I will not go away.
- 是的 - 我不会走开
OK thanks
好，谢谢
Good day
再会
- I was relieved that it ended well. - True.
- 结局很好，我松了口气 - 是的
-I knew it would end well. -Yes.
-我知道结局会很好。- 是的
- That's right, Gun Woo. - Yes?
- 是的，建宇 - 是吗？
Remember the question Mr. Choi asked Jang Do Im about the gold bullion?
还记得崔先生向张道任提出的关于金条的问题吗？
Yes, and how is In Beom the only one who knows her whereabouts?
是啊，怎么只有仁范知道她的下落呢？
Yes
是的
How much do you think it is worth?
您认为它值多少钱？
I don't know
我不知道
I think it's worth tens of billions.
我认为价值数百亿。
Good
好的
That includes the money he stole from Mr. Choi, right?
这其中包括他从崔先生那里偷来的钱吧？
correct
正确的
If the cops don't catch Myung Gil Kim,
如果警察不抓到金明吉
He will take the money and gold and flee out of the country.
他将带着金钱和黄金逃出该国。
"We can't let that happen. This is Mr. Choi's money."
“我们不能让这种事发生。 这是崔先生的钱。”
let's get ready
让我们准备好
Let's hunt him down and beat him to death.
我们去追捕他，把他打死吧。
Seems like a good idea.
似乎是个好主意。
- Let's drink ourselves unconscious tonight! - Great!
- 今晚让我们喝得不省人事！ - 太棒了！
- Beom, Joon-min, well done! - Sir!
- Beom，Joon-min，干得好！ - 先生！
Well, let's continue drinking at my house!
好吧，我们继续去我家喝酒吧！
What is the matter
什么事
Do you smell something?
你闻到什么味道了吗？
Eun-seo, what's wrong?
恩熙，怎么了？
Well, it smells like smoke I guess.
嗯，我猜它闻起来像烟味。
Stay calm.
保持冷静。
do not you dare
你敢
the curse
诅咒
Aden.
亚丁。
"(Tae Ho Choi)"
“（崔泰浩）”
- Where are you? - I'm working overtime, sir.
- 你在哪里？ - 我正在加班，先生。
I'll send a driver with a phone now.
我现在就派一个带电话的司机过来。
Find someone for me.
为我找一个人。
How many people?
多少人？
We'll start with an old man.
我们先从一位老人开始。
-Is it such an emergency? -If I find him by tomorrow afternoon,
-有这么紧急的事吗？ -如果我明天下午之前找到他
I will pay you three times your wage.
我将支付你三倍的工资。
Your order, sir.
您的命令，先生。
“Unit No. 1 of the Serious Crimes Investigation Division”
“重罪调查科第一组”
Translation of "Walid Muharram"
“瓦利德穆哈拉姆”的翻译